(Mayumi) Is there anyone... is there anyone?
(Mayumi's heavy breathing)
There are, right?
Please forgive me now
Are you watching it?
someone…
Already... please
(sound of door opening)
(whistle)
(footsteps)
You're a teacher, right?
(Sanada) You know me well.
(Mayumi) Don't you like it? this
(Sanada) Is this your first time teaching?
(Mayumi) Guidance...
(Sanada) 2nd year group D No. 22 Mayumi Takahashi
Japanese 3
English 3 Social Studies 3
Science 1 Mathematics 1
158cm 42kg
From above...
85 57 84
Size 7
virgin
My performance as a disciplinary committee member is the worst.
Why are you doing this?
Reason for detention...
June 4th 12th period Current country class
criticize the teacher's writing
without persistently changing one's opinion
then for 30 seconds
disrupted the class
Are you sure?
Because… “Saka” in Osaka is
Because it's not a problem
(Sanada) Which one is better?
What is it?
(Sanada) Choose.
Hurry... choose!
(Frightened breathing)
(Sanada) Huh?
For the first time...
You chose a good one
what do you mean?
What I'm going to make you drink from now on...
this is water
Stop...
I beg you…
I beg you! Please forgive me now
I won't do it anymore...
sorry…
It seems like I haven't studied enough yet.
I have enough… I have enough!
I won't do it anymore...
I beg you!
(Sanada) Yes, hmm.
yes
Takahashi-kun
(Mayumi) Sorry...
sorry! Stop it
That's why I have to study hard today.
ah…
(scream)
(sound of glass breaking)
(footsteps)
Who is it?
(quite masked breathing)
What? you
You have a good hobby, don't you?
(Sanada) Uh... ah!
Here we go!
Wow!
You're going to do it...
(quite masked breathing)
(Mayumi) No, no!
No more... please stop!
sorry
please! I won't do it anymore
Please excuse me
(the sound of footsteps moving away)
(siren)
(whistle sound)
♪〜
Ah...!
〜♪
(Teacher) Late night at 25:22
A teacher from our school is teaching in the instruction room.
A naked female student with a mask breaks in.
He assaulted a teacher and then ran away.
Something like a third-page newspaper article happened here.
What happened at this Sparta Academy, which boasts a 100% university entrance rate.
The culprit is a female student
A janitor cleaning
A naked woman was seen running from the school building to the entrance of the dormitory.
That means the culprit is among you.
(snore)
(Teacher) Mr. Inoue
That's good courage
(Inoue) Sorry!
Violation of school rules
guide!
Disciplinary Committee!
(Inoue) Please give me a break!
To the instruction room
please!
Hey Takahashi!
You're also a member of the public morals committee.
What are you absent-minded?
(Chigusa) Let's go
but…
I'm going
Mayumi!
(Inoue) Help me... please!
(Chigusa) Sorry.
(Inoue) Please, please! I'll do anything
(Chigusa) No!
Mayumi!
I wonder what will happen if I go there...
(Inoue) Release the dog!
Don't get carried away just because you're a virgin!
Come on, let's go
Wait... just a moment
(Inoue) No... no, no!
No, no... no!
Ah!
(cough cough)
No, no, no... no!
No! Oh no!
(Inoue screams)
What do you mean?
(Akiko) Pretty mask
(Member) 1 liter of hot water every day
And blankets provided
Sorry, unlike the photography club, the newspaper club isn't starving.
(Satan's toenails) Please come here.
why is she naked
home…
(Satan's toenails) Why are you naked?
yes…
I don't understand
Ugh... Wow!
(cough cough)
(footsteps)
(Satan's Toenails) Do you know why she is naked?
(Yowai) In this Sparta school where weapons are limited
It can be said that this is the most effective fighting method for female students to choose.
Any man would let his guard down when he saw this.
and…
Because we instinctively look at things, we create gaps.
Above all...
The determination to die that comes from facing the enemy naked
If all of this is calculated
It can be said that she is a terrifyingly clever woman.
It's not easy
(Satan's Toenail) Isn't he a pretty good student?
Pretty mask
(laughter)
(Satan's toenails) Her search is
I'm thinking of asking him in the future.
What do you think?
Haha...
He's like Taiboku.
what? that
Please don't rush
Well, that's the reason why it's not popular.
Wha... how do you know?
I know something else
What led me to choose biology
I wanted to dissect a female animal.
I guess he's trying to find a balance so that women don't treat him like that.
That's right!
(Sanada) Wow! (Age) Yeah!
Let me tell you two good things today.
“Heaven creates man above man”
what? that
Ugh!
(age) Huh!
And one more thing
“The pen is mightier than the sword”
(Sound of ruler falling)
Excuse me, was it a ruler?
(Satan's Toenails) I'm glad it was as expected.
thank you
(Emi) Isn't it really bad?
Will you call me again?
she is fighting alone
(Chigusa) No!
(Emi) Huh?
(Chigusa) Will anyone be happy to read that?
(Mayumi) All the students will be happy.
(Chigusa) Is it just you?
(Mayumi) What does it mean?
(Chigusa) You just feel indebted.
different from other students
(Mayumi) The guys from the photography club from earlier?
Not only
Look
All the students are looking for her.
Like a starving stray dog
The food in front of me is more important than the favor I received.
The more I tell people about her successes, the more
It only increases its value as food.
Leave it alone
Manager, you knew, right?
what's going on over there
Even though you know, why would you hand it over like that?
Yeah
(Mayumi) Are the teachers happy to do that?
That's right
(Mayumi) Are you going to overlook that?
What will happen if we do something?
I just have to get through it! Until graduation
She mustered up the courage to stand up on her own.
You're not brave, you're just an idiot!
teeth?
(footsteps)
Oh... take it easy.
From that day onwards
My name is Juro Rei and I have been appointed as a teacher at our school.
Oh!
Huh~
That's a good article
The passion of the writer can be seen everywhere.
But it's rejected
It's a waste~ Let's make this the top article.
That authority rests with me as the manager.
(Age) Ah...
I see. I'm sorry, I was too impulsive.
Then give me that
What are you going to do?
Hmm... I'll use it in class.
This is a good example of how to approach social issues.
The school is not silent about the content, right?
That's okay! Please leave it to me
hey?
Excuse me
It seems contrived
What are you looking at?
(chime)
Dangerous extracurricular class end
I went back
How far have you followed me?
You over there
(Mayumi) Huh...?
Ah... yeah hehe...
(Member) Manager, isn't it about time?
(Club member) Isn't he here today?
(Akiko) No! still!
Is it really around here?
(Akiko) It's true.
What information? that
It's a hunch!
Guess...
Are you searching for two hours based on your intuition?
Shut up and search!
(Akiko) Ah! (Member) Manager!
(Member) Are you okay?
(Age) Haha What are you doing?
(Club member) I was looking for a mask...
It's against school rules to go outside during class.
Sorry!
Please refrain from giving instructions.
It was the photography club, right?
yes…
Were you the manager?
(Akiko) Are you going to rape me today too?
(Age) Akiko Suzuki, 2nd year class E, number 10
All grades are 5 or excellent.
From top 83 60 87
Not a virgin
I was told that if you catch one, you'll get meat for your meal.
I'm in a hurry
That's not all, right?
I looked into you.
Yuuka hates Chigusa and Mayumi Takahashi, right?
“Even though I had better grades, those two were the only ones chosen to be on the disciplinary committee.”
Poor guy
But I like the virgins at my school.
I was just betrayed by a man!
What's wrong with that?
Let's correct the last sentence of the research report.
Investigators sometimes make mistakes.
Let's just say that after looking into it, I found out that she was actually a virgin.
hey?
Instead...
(Teacher) Hey, what are you going to do?
Hey, what should we do?
I'm listening, answer me!
(Student) Ah...
(Teacher) I heard you, so answer!
(Student) Good morning! (Teacher) Yes.
(Student) Good morning! (Teacher) Yes!
(Student) Good morning.
(age) Good morning!
good morning! It's a refreshing morning
thank you!
(Sanada) Hmph.
Today, everyone will have their underwear inspected before class.Stand up on your desk.
Show me
Yeah okay
Second-rate!
what up? Raise it quickly
What? that underwear
Ugh...
(Sanada) Why aren't you wearing this?
I tried to wear it
But... when I woke up in the morning, it wasn't there.
A stupid lie...
Well, the full moon is near, so you're feeling horny, right?
picture…?
Take it off quickly
now here
Like that...
(Sanada) One more violation added.
The only answer to me is “yes”
Get on your hands and knees and I'll make you wear it.
(Emi) No... (Sanada) Hey... Hey!
(Age) “I wonder who is the mask?”
picture?
Hehe, that's what you look like.
I guess I like it a lot
(Mayumi) Well...
I would also like to meet you once.
(Mayumi) Huh...?
“Captivating the hearts of students”
This is very important for teachers
I would love to meet and learn
Teacher, why did you come to this school?
(Age) Wait a minute… Wait a minute
It's okay
Don't tell that to anyone.
Actually, I'm a spy from the Ministry of Education, Culture, Sports, Science and Technology.
spy?
yes
I came to investigate this school.
Is it true?
yes!
No... it's not interesting.
(Age) I think it's natural to have questions about the school.
Even if it's for the purpose of going to higher education, that kind of punishment is not good.
i want to change that
(Mayumi) What I think is right
Have you ever been told that you were wrong?
(Age) I see.
There are many.
(Mayumi) What do you think we should do in such a case?
(Age) If you think it's true, follow that belief!
What should I do when I still lose even if I tell the truth?
You should say it!
Why?
(Age) Courage is transmitted, right?
The person who saw it will appear next
And in the end the truth wins
the pen is mightier than the sword
And...
(scream)
(Emi) Ah...! no…
School regulations Article 73
Don't walk down the hallway on your butt
One more violation added.
(Emi) Please forgive me!
It's true! Really...
I'll give you lots of pampering so I won't do something like this again.
Now, quickly get down on all fours
(Emi) No... no!
(Age) What are you doing?
(Mayumi) Emi!
(Sanada) It has nothing to do with you.
(Age) It has something to do with it!
It's about my important students.
Mr. Sanada
First of all, those who teach and those who learn
Isn't it important to trust each other?
trust?
Trust is useless
What children need...
It's scary
(Mayumi) Ah Emi!
(Sanada) Wait (age) Hey!
(Mayumi) Are you okay? (Age) Ah...
I'm fine
More than that...
Are you ready?
(Mayumi) Please stop it!
Oh, are you trying to disturb me?
School designated underwear
On the contrary, I lose concentration!
Are you going against the school?
teeth clenched
Wow!
Sister!
ah…
You're here, pretty masked
(Sanada) I'll pay back the debt I owed during this time.
Look!
(pretty masked) Yeah! (Sanada) Wow!
(Sanada) Wow!
Wow! Ugh...
(shutter sound)
(Akiko) Go!
(Member) Well!
(Member) Come on!
Ah... Ugh!
Don't come!
What is it? You
Shall I tell the teacher?
transformation!
(quite masked breathing)
What is it? transformation!
(quite masked gasping voice)
transformation!
(scream)
Ho-oh
(Satan's Toenail) What, are you calm?
I found it
Weakness of Kekko Kamen
(quite masked heavy breathing)
(Akiko) Pervert! transformation! transformation! …
(knock)
what? What will you do if you find out?
You know...
I'll ask you directly
Are you the manager?
picture?
What are you doing?
They look alike.
The bust line is good, the smell is good.
to whom?
Quite a mask!
What if?
like…
really like!
Hey, make me your disciple.
Me too...
No, I'm not quite a mask.
Because...
Besides, I also have something to say about Mr. Age.
I don't care about that
It doesn't matter!
You're too close to that teacher.
not a good teacher
Yes, especially in front of Mayumi.
What does it mean?
Doesn't it feel intentional?
not at all
Hey, think about it
We need a teacher whose principal will be on our side.
Do you think I'll hire you?
i trust the teacher
Is it expensive?
What?
You'll know when your trust has been betrayed
As expected, it's different
(Chigusa) Huh?
If you're wearing a mask, you're such a good teacher, I won't doubt you.
Enough already
(Age) Ah! there was
(Mayumi) Huh?
What happened?
Yes, uh... the school principal will be coming soon.
Apparently they're forming a specialized team to capture the mask.
If the project is carried out
No matter how much it's a mask...
It's hard... What should I do?
That's why I want to make the first move no matter what.
If only I knew the identity
I think there is a way to contact you.
But how?
(age) Takahashi-kun... like you
I heard from a student who actually met her.
Could you please put it together?
Understood
I'll protect my sister no matter what.
Yeah
(knock)
(Chigusa) What?
Hey, please tell me the truth
Eh... what?
Be honest with me only
So you're saying it's different, right?
Because I know!
I don't have time anyway
(Chigusa) Oh wait!
(Mayumi) It's okay.
Hey, it was Yuuka-kun.
Do you need something?
Ask them about it
(Mayumi) Wait...wait a minute.
Get out of the way!
(Mayumi) What? What?
(Member) Please step back for a moment.
(Chigusa) Hey... let me go!
(Member) Excuse me! (Chigusa) Ugh!
Teacher, what is this?
Gained trust is returned through betrayal
terrible!
This is common knowledge in world history.
(Chigusa) Ordinary students did this to the disciplinary committee.
Do you think it will be free?
(Akiko) I'm no longer a normal student.
(Chigusa) A non-virgin cannot become a disciplinary committee member.
(Akiko) Investigators sometimes make mistakes.
(Chigusa) Are you trying to say that you're not a virgin?
(Member) What are you saying to the manager? This pervert
(Member) Apologize! This pervert
i'm not a pervert
(Akiko) If you don't admit it honestly, your hymen might break.
(Chigusa) What?
(Member) Yeah! (Chigusa) Ah!
(Mayumi) No... stop it!
(Member) Come on! (Member) Get out of the way!
(Akiko) Disturbers are out! (Member) Yes
(Member) Come here!
(Mayumi) Let go!
(Member) Don't get angry!
gentlemen!
Isn't it painful to hear so many lies?
I'm not lying
Takahashi-kun...
The truth is, just showing courage is not enough!
I need strength!
(Member) Come! Let me go (Mayumi)...
Mayumi!
(Member) Admit it quickly!
(Member) Hey!
(Member) Apologize quickly!
(Member) Admit it quickly!
(Member) Admit it!
oh~
Wasn't it Yuuka Chigusa?
(Akiko) Let me show you the results of our research, perverted woman!
(Member) Pervert! (Member) Pervert!
When someone calls me a pervert, I lose myself in anger.
That is your weakness!
(Member) Pervert woman (Akiko) Pervert!
(Member) Perverted woman! (Member) Pervert bastard
(Akiko) Pervert!
(quite a masked gasp)
minister! minister
Ugh... Ugh!
(Sound of pain)
(scream)
(cough cough)
(quite a masked gasp)
(Member) Perverted woman!
(Member) Pervert (Member) Pervert!
(Mayumi's scream)
Ugh...! ah~!
(Growling)
(Akiko's scream)
(Member) Manager!
(Age) Shall we chase?
(Mayumi) Manager!
It's okay, just a little while
(Akiko) Wait, pervert!
(Akiko) Die, pervert!
(Member) Wait, perverted woman! (Member) Wait!
(Mayumi's breathing)
(Mayumi) It's okay here.
Wait a minute, sister, I'll help you.
(Chigusa) You...
When did you become so strong?
I'm not strong, I just want to be free
That's cool
Please miss it
(Age) Nun!
(Chigusa) Mayumi!
What are you doing?
Spartan style torture 78-4 Pumpkin enema
(Mayumi) Pumpkin...? (Sanada) Oh
Don't worry
My usual punishment enema is 100% glycerin.
This one is 70%
After all, some people die.
Well, let's enjoy it slowly
No... please stop!
Please... just don't do that!
Don't worry, you'll only be embarrassed once in a while.
Stop it!
Why do you do that?
(Satan's toenails) There's no particular meaning.
(Chigusa) What?
(Satan's Toenails) I want to hear your screams.
(Mayumi) Please!
(Sanada) Should I let go of my strength? Takahashi: Take a deep breath.
Ah, you're not wearing designated underwear either, you're a helpless girl.
(Mayumi) No!
(Sanada) Good job.
(Sanada) Let's go! (Mayumi) No!
(Sanada) Wow!
Here it is!
You... take my pumpkin enema!
(Chigusa) Ugh!
(Mayumi) I'll put up with anything except pumpkin.
(Sanada) How do I feel about pumpkin? Hey!
(Chigusa) Okay, Mayumi!
I won't let them hear your screams!
(Sanada) He's very energetic.
(Chigusa) Uh...
(Sanada) I wonder how long I can keep slapping my mouth!
Until you get a girlfriend
That's a lie
(Sanada) Why don't you just give up?
Pretty mask
By now, they're getting really hard on me.
Your allies of justice are no longer here!
that's why?
(Sanada) What?
I won't lose to you even if I don't have a mask!
(Sanada) Oh...
If you inherit the will of the masked mask
I need to dress more embarrassingly!
Look!
(sound of door opening)
(footsteps)
Sister!
(Sanada) Here you come, perverted woman.
You are a poison to my eyes
(pretty masked) Ah...
(Sanada) Pervert
what up? transformation
(age) You're breathing hard, pervert!
(quite a masked gasp)
(Sanada) Metamorphosis (age) Metamorphosis
(Age) What's wrong, you pervert?
(Sanada) Hey!
(age) Wow!
(Sanada) Wow...
Wow!
(age) Strong...
Huh! Haa!
(pretty masked) Ah!
(Age) Hey!
Wow!
Ha! Ha! Ha!
Ha! Ha!
(pretty masked) Ugh...! (age) hahaha
(quite a masked and distressed voice)
(gasp)
(Age) Hmm.
Wow!
No way...
Maybe he was just happy to be called a pervert...
(Satan's toenails) It's not fun otherwise.
I'll give you a scar that can't be hidden with a mask.
Huh!
Haa!
Wow!
(quite a masked and distressed voice)
Sister, don't give up!
Pretty mask, don't lose!
(quite a mask) Wow!
(Satan's toenails) Hah... hah~
(Satan's toenails) Ah!
Sister! Sister! Sister! …
♪〜
〜♪